<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nirant Kasliwal on</title><link>https://nirantk.com/</link><description>Recent content in Nirant Kasliwal on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright (c) 2018-Present Nirant K</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nirantk.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Endorsed Friends</title><link>https://nirantk.com/endorsed/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/endorsed/</guid><description>Talented friends I can endorse for their work &amp;ndash; either because I&amp;rsquo;ve worked with them or know them socially.
I&amp;rsquo;m happy to connect you with them if you&amp;rsquo;re looking to hire or collaborate with them, with double opt-in from both sides.
Name Skills Remarks/Notes Endorsed By Shubhi Saxena Engineer-turned-early-Product: PLG, Pre-Sales, Sales or Marketing Was an anchoring and energetic friend for the GenerativeAI DeepHack which we did together Nirant Dhruv Anand Search Consultant, VectorDB &amp;amp; LLM ex-CMU, Google &amp;amp; Meta Know him via the GenerativeAI Community Nirant Sudarshan Chandra Babu Generative Image Models Former Enterpreneur, know him via the GenerativeAI Community Nirant Anudeep ML Engineer Was the category winner at the GenerativeAI Hackathon Nirant Kshitij ML Engineer - Sudarshan Eepsita Gupta SaaS Positioning Has worked with the likes of Capillary, Vymo, DHL.</description></item><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://nirantk.com/introduction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/introduction/</guid><description>If you&amp;rsquo;re visiting this page, it means you&amp;rsquo;re likely a founder or VC interested in working with me. I&amp;rsquo;m going to use this document to describe how I choose projects and split my work between advisory work and consulting. If it all makes sense, shoot me an email at hello@nirantk.com.
Picking Projects #
I prioritize projects based on three key factors: High-Value Projects: I seek projects that leverage my expertise and create significant impact for founders, and in return, equitable compensation.</description></item><item><title>Generative AI Community: General Guide</title><link>https://nirantk.com/community/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Jun 2023 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/community/</guid><description>Rules #
✅ - Please do these behaviours!
❌ - These may result in bans
👎 - we discourage these behaviours, but context matters
These guides are good rules of thumbs for behaviour, but admins reserve all rights to remove or ban members or conversations.
Content Sharing #
✅ Things that you find interesting, curious or noteworthy around AI research, philosophy, implementation and future. Also new tools or how you’re using them.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://nirantk.com/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 13:59:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/about/</guid><description>As a consultant and advisor:
I specialize in working with Early stage founders, 0 to 1 stage of product development or later stage, adding a new feature to an existing product For non-coding founders, I act as a tour guide for advanced AI technologies - improving their understanding of potential applications and limitations alike This includes things like LLMs and Vector Databases, which are amazing tools which unlock a lot of new, intelligent value but also have their own limits.</description></item><item><title>Generative AI Hack Demos</title><link>https://nirantk.com/deephackdemos/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 08:49:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/deephackdemos/</guid><description>👋 You&amp;rsquo;ve landed at the perfect spot to check out all the coolest demos from the #GenerativeAIHack.
🧑‍🤝‍🧑 90+ hackers on Day 1, 150+ folks at Demo day
⚡️ 43 submissions, 32 in-person, 11 remote from 6 cities
🙏 13 sponsors from 3 countries, 2 Open Source Software companies: Weaviate, AppSmith
🤗 20% raised from individual donors or collectives of them
💰 5 Lakh INR in Prizes
I&amp;rsquo;m super stoked to share these mind-blowing projects with you—created by some seriously talented folks from all corners of the world.</description></item><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://nirantk.com/writing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:49:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/writing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Docs</title><link>https://nirantk.com/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/docs/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>