<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Drafts on Nirant Kasliwal</title><link>https://nirantk.com/drafts.html</link><description>Recent content in Drafts on Nirant Kasliwal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:09:00 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nirantk.com/drafts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dos and Don'ts for ML Hiring</title><link>https://nirantk.com/drafts/ml-hiring.html</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 00:09:00 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/drafts/ml-hiring.html</guid><description>Do Seniormost hire first: Start by hiring the senior most person you&amp;rsquo;re going to hire. E.g. start by hiring the ML Lead (assuming you already have a CTO) Have a means to tell that your investment in data science is working out or not Closest to User first: Hire the person who will consume the data to build for the user first Sourcing: Begin sourcing early and over-emphasise two channels: Referrals and Portfolios Typically, in India - expect: ~2 months to close a full time role at early career (0-3 years) and ~3 months to close a mid career (3-7 years) and 6+ months to close a senior hire If a developer has open source code contributions in the last 2-3 years, consider waving off the coding or algorithmic challenge to speed up the interview process Pay above market cash salaries In 12-18 months from now, when your ML Engineer will have internalised all the requirements, company culture and built a bunch of important tooling - she would get an offer which is 2-3x of today.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nirantk.com/drafts/beware-of-false-binaries.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/drafts/beware-of-false-binaries.html</guid><description>Binaries and boundaries are useful as mental heuristics for decision making, but they are also handicaps. It&amp;rsquo;s stupid to play the sport of life with a handicap.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nirantk.com/drafts/bigco-vs-startups.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/drafts/bigco-vs-startups.html</guid><description>https://danluu.com/startup-tradeoffs/#fnref:S
Beyond First 90 Days - 2 Less Obvious Ideas
I am assuming that you already know the hygiene factors: Make few promises. Keep most of them and exceed few of them atleast. Get to like the top 5% in the skill of effort estimation for your own work at the very least. And so on.
Contribute to Developer Ecosystem Improving any part of the developer ecosystem is useful and visible at the same time.</description></item></channel></rss>