<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>production ml on Nirant Kasliwal</title><link>https://nirantk.com/tags/production-ml.html</link><description>Recent content in production ml on Nirant Kasliwal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:18 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nirantk.com/tags/production-ml/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1M OpenAI Benchmark: PGVector vs VectorDB (Qdrant)</title><link>https://nirantk.com/writing/pgvector-vs-qdrant.html</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/writing/pgvector-vs-qdrant.html</guid><description>1M OpenAI Benchmark: pgvector vs VectorDB (Qdrant) You may have considered using PostgreSQL&amp;rsquo;s pgvector extension for vector similarity search. There are good reasons why this option is strictly inferior to dedicated vector search engines, such as Qdrant.
We ran both benchmarks using the vectordb framework solely dedicated to processing vector data. The difference in performance is quite staggering.
Query Speed Final results show that pgvector lags behind Qdrant by a factor of 20 when it comes to throughput.</description></item><item><title>ML Model Monitoring</title><link>https://nirantk.com/writing/modelmonitoring.html</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Sep 2019 00:00:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/writing/modelmonitoring.html</guid><description>Mayank asked on Twitter:
Some ideas/papers/tools on monitoring models in production. A use case would be say a classification task over large inputs. I want to visualise how are the predicted values or even confidence scores vary over time? (paraphrased)
Quick Hacks pandas-profiling If you are logging confidence scores, you can begin there. The quickest hack is to visualize with pandas-profiling: https://github.com/pandas-profiling/pandas-profiling/
Rolling means Calculate rolling aggregates (e.g. mean, variance) of your confidence scores.</description></item></channel></rss>