<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>personal on Nirant Kasliwal</title><link>https://nirantk.com/tags/personal.html</link><description>Recent content in personal on Nirant Kasliwal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 23:29:18 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nirantk.com/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Now</title><link>https://nirantk.com/now.html</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2021 23:29:18 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/now.html</guid><description>What I’m doing now Work:
After almost 6 months of full time Machine Learning consulting/career break, I&amp;rsquo;ve moved to a role away from the data science field. I’m now working as a Software Engineer at Sundial.so.
Last Updated in December 2021 from Bengaluru, India
The concept of now page is from Derek Sivers</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nirantk.com/about.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/about.html</guid><description>Me in 10 seconds I am a Machine Learning consultant with a focus on NLP (including search &amp;amp; speech) &amp;amp; Vision systems for 0 to 1 startups.
I&amp;rsquo;ve worked in Machine Learning for almost ~5 years, and have written a book on Natural Language Processing. Dr. Andrew Ng recommends my work to his CS230 students at Stanford. My blogs have been appreciated by Noble Laureate Dr. Paul Romer.
I live in Bengaluru, but grew up in Surat, Gujarat.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://nirantk.com/anthony.html</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nirantk.com/anthony.html</guid><description>Hey Anthony!
Here is why we should talk:
I&amp;rsquo;ve built datasets for a while. Here are some which I released to open sources: Hindi2vec &amp;ndash; this dataset is now part of the IndicGlue task web here, look for BBC News Articles, Code switching in Hindi-&amp;gt;English: Hinglish, ACL SemEval Paper here, code I worked as a Data Engineer at Sundial.so &amp;ndash; working with Dagster, data quality guardrails, picked up bits about data security, worked with data warehouses like Redshift with dbt.</description></item></channel></rss>